24小时
第三季  第12集
前情提要
-你好 雪莉  -大卫
-Hello, Sherry.  -David.
艾伦决意让韦恩走人
Alan's determined to see Wayne removed
即使意味着毁掉我的总统职位
even if it means destroying my presidency.
你要我找些东西对付艾伦?
You want me to find something you can use against Alan?
你以为你可以让你的神经质前妻编造些谎言来整垮我?
You think you can enlist your psychopathic ex-wife to manufacture lies about me in order to bring me down?
如果你不想这样 就离我弟弟远点
You wanna to stop, stay away from my brother.
杰克 我想是阿马多尔
Jack, I think it's Amador.
我拿到货了 在波斯塔米塔东边有个旧矿
I've got the product. There's an old mine east of Post Mita.
1小时10分钟后在最北面的建筑里碰头
Meet me in the northern most building in an hour and 10 minutes.
安全起见我会带一个人
I'll have one man with me for security,
你也可以这样做
you may do the same.
-事情是你搞出来的  -现在继续太冒险了
-You're falling through with what you have started.  -There are too many risks now.
这是不可避免的
They are inavoidable.
反恐局 德斯勒
CTU, Dessler.
拉姆 如果你想做交易 那我们现在就得走了
Ramon, if you want the deal happen, we've got to go now.
托尼 是杰克 他打电话给我们呢
Tony, Jack's on the line. He's using a cells one way.
阿马多尔大概1小时后到波斯塔米塔的一个旧矿那
Amador's gonna be at the mine in Post Mita in about an hour.
我们也需要差不多的时间赶到那里
It's gonna take us that long to get there
让你的人就位
and get your men into position.
断线了
It's disconnected.
根据反恐局从杰克那得到的消息 应该是在这交易
Based on what CTU got from Jack, the meeting will probably take place here.
我将前进到这个位置
My forward position's gonna be here.
我要你的人都在这个安全区域内 直到我们确定病毒是真的
What I need from you is to put your men behind this range until we know that the virus is real.
你的人多久才能赶到旧矿?
How long will it take to get your men to the old mine?
90秒
90 seconds.
祝你们走运
Good luck.
雷蒙
Ramon
如果你想做交易 那我们现在就得走了
If you want this deal to happen, we have to leave now.
我们必须比阿马多尔早20分钟赶到旧矿
We have to be at the mine 20 minutes before Amador gets there.
交易取消
The deal is off.
我们现在就走
We're leaving now.
赫克托!
Hector!
以下事件发生于凌晨12点至1点之间
The following takes place between 12:00 am and 1:00 am.
你们都准备好了吗?
Are you people ready?
嗯 已就绪
Yeah, they're waiting.
克萝伊呢?
What about Chloe?
嗯 她也准备好了
Yeah, she's there too.
很好 这是我们得到的病毒的机会
Alright, this is our one chance to get the virus.
确保他们都知道面临什么样的危险
So make sure they're all aware of what's at stake.
他们知道了
They're aware.
我只想说接下来1小时将发生的...
I'm just saying that it's all gonna come down in the next hour.
你知道 托尼 你没必要一直强调...
You know, Tony. You don't have to keep reminding...
不 我必须要
Yes, I do.
听着 已经出了太多差错
Look, too many things did go wrong here,
我们不能再犯错了
we don't need another mistake.
嗯
So,
最近几分钟我们有跟杰克联络上吗?
we had a communication from jack in the last few minutes?
没有
No.
他还和尼娜和萨拉扎兄弟在一起
He's still with Nina and the Salazars.
你应该听我的话
You should have listened to me.
这是我的事业 我亲手建立起来的
This is my business. I built it.
我不会让任何人毁掉它
I won't let anyone destroy it.
即使是你
Not even you.
雷蒙...
Ramon...
血止不住 我们得送他去医院
We can't stop the bleeding. We gotta get him to the hospital.
不行
We can't.
会被怀疑的
They'll ask questions.
不去他会死掉的
He'll die if we don't.
我知道
I know.
雷蒙...
Ramon...
拉姆 我很遗憾
Ramon, I'm sorry.
但是我们必须走了
But we have to go.
等我们完成交易后
When we're done,
我要好好安葬他
I want him to have a proper burial.
雷蒙
Ramon
你在犯个大错
You're making a big mistake.
他给你下了圈套
He's setting you up.
他为反恐局工作
He works for CTU.
赫克托是对的
Hector was right.
你该放弃的
You should give this up.
够了
That's enough.
永远别提我弟弟的名字
Don't mention my brother's name, ever.
好了 我们去交易吧
Alright. Let's do the deal.
大家都回车上
Everybody back in the cars.
通知反恐局
Inform CTU.
每半小时通知我最新进展
I want update in every half hour.
-请进?  -大卫
-Yes?  -david,
我只是来告诉你我要走了
I just want you to know that I'm leaving.
你抓到了米利肯什么把柄?
What's leverage you have with Milican?
我告诉过你 大卫 你现在最好不要知道详情
I told you David, it's better that you don't know the details right now.
好吧
All right.
亚伦告诉我你拒绝特勤部的陪同
Aaron told me that you refused the secret service's escort.
是 因为如果我不是一个人去的话 那会吓到我要见的人
Yes, but that's because the person I'm going to see might be scared if I don't come alone.
不用为我担心
Don't worry about me.
我能照顾自己的
I can take care of myself.
我知道
I know you can.
大卫
David
我一直相信你的领导能力
I still believe in your presidency
如果艾伦妨碍到你对国家的领导
and if Alan milican is threatening your ability to lead this country,
我会阻止他的
he will be stopped.
阿马多尔会在30分钟后将病毒带到这个地方
Amador's bringing the virus to this location in 30 minutes.
特种部队埋伏在距此2分钟路程的地方
We have delta team's bunker 2 minutes away.
只要杰克确认包裹里有病毒 我们马上截下病毒
We will intercept the package as soon as jack confirms it contain the virus.
杰克的通讯器好用了吗?
Jack's transmitter working yet?
没有 我们有蔡斯
No, we're using Chase.
他隐蔽在前线给我们传送确认信息
He's moving into forward covert position to give us confirmation.
他能给我们和特种部队传送声音
He'll be able to transmit sound both to us and delta teams.
谁在处理这个?
Who's running his com?
是我 没有现行的程式
I am. There weren't any protocol in place.
但我写了个程序来放大低频声音信号并转发出去
I wrote a software to amplify the low frequency audio signal and relay it out.
好 很好
Okay, good.
交易一结束 杰克拿到病毒 蔡斯会马上通知我们
After that, Chase will let us know when the transaction's complete and Jack has the virus.
那时候我们就行动 采取充分预防措施保证病毒的安全
At which point our units to move in taking full precautious to keep that virus safe.
雷蒙
Ramon
让你的人在阿马多尔到之前隐蔽起来
You have to get your men out of sight before Amador arrives.
我知道 我们会暗中盯着他的
I know. But we will be seeing him in sight.
好了 把包给我
Alright, give me the bag.
叫他们都提高警惕
Tell them to keep their eyes open.
拉姆 这是他的圈套 我可以证明
Ramon, he is setting you up I can prove it.
真的?
Really?
怎么证明?
How?
我在反恐局待了7年 我知道他们的规程
I was in CTU for 7 years, I know their protocols.
我知道他们怎么做
I know how they play this.
说
I'm listening.
他们的战术部队不会离的很近
Their tact teams won't be too close.
但正常情况下他们至少会派一个人监视我们
They'll have at least one man during the common sense that is watching us now.
你知道那个人会在哪吗?
And you know where that man would be?
正前方的一些高地
Straight ahead, there's some high ground.
如果没有就看看向西90度的树林
Nobody's there, or 90 degrees to west to the tree line.
我们很快就会知道有没有人了
We'll know soon enough.
菲利普·巴勃罗 去查一下
Philip, Pablo, check it out.
从边上包抄过去 也许她说的是真的
Make sure you make your approach from the sides in case this woman is right.
我说的是真的
I am right.
金
Kim
我需要你来一下 这些格式变了
I need you to go. These format changes.
好 这些文件要重编页码 硬盘上没有
Yeah. Here you gonna need those files to repagination. They're not on the hard drive.
-那是什么?  -孩子
-What is that?  -It's a baby.
嗯 我看得出是个孩子
Yeah. I can see it's a baby.
谁的孩子?
Whose baby is it?
-克萝伊的  -克萝伊的?
-Chloe's.  -Chloe's?
她孩子的保姆家里有急事
Her baby sitter's having some sort of family emergencies.
金 克萝伊没有孩子
kim, Chloe doesn't have a baby.
她当然有
Of course she does.
不 她没有
No, she doesn't.
我曾跟克萝伊在搜查组共事 我们都做过背景调查 人际关系调查 身体检查等等
I was in the search team with Chloe. We've had background check, personal tree, medical tree, those things.
她从没有孩子?
She's never had a baby?
没 这肯定不是她的孩子
No, it's definitely not her kid.
菲利普·巴勃罗 报告你们的位置
Philip, Pablo, call me your position.
拉姆 我是菲利普
Ramon, it's Philip.
你在哪?
Where are you?
在树林 这里没人
At the tree line, there's no one here.
巴勃罗 你呢?
Pablo, what about you?
巴勃罗?
Pablo?
巴勃罗 你听到了吗?
Pablo, can you hear me?
他们抓住他了
They got him.
巴勃罗
Pablo?
他死了 拉姆 下一个就是你
He's dead, Ramon. And come for you next.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
你跟他说什么了?
What did you say to him?
雷蒙
Ramon
是我
It's me.
我在高地这
I'm at the high ground.
有什么发现?
Do you see anything?
没有
No.
这没人
There's no one here.
嗯 很好
Alright, good.
原地待命
Hold your position.
-提高警惕  -好
-And keep your eyes open.  -Okay.
把对讲机丢了
Drop the walkie.
别再说谎了
No more lies of you.
阿马多尔15分钟后到达
Amador will be here in 15 minutes.
你过去拿病毒 并把钱给他
Go front and get the virus. Give him his money
然后再把病毒给我们
and bring the virus back to us.
我派个人作你保镖
You'll have one of our men with you acting as your bodyguard.
但是如果你想要逃跑
But if you try to escape
或者跟阿马多尔多说一个字
or communicate anything to Amador,
我们会杀了你
we'll kill you.
就算他失手了 山头上还有3个人拿着狙击枪 瞄准着你的脑袋呢
If he misses, there are 3 men in the hills with sniper rifle aiming at your head.
想活命就乖乖完成交易
If you want to live, make sure this deal happens.
-我明白  -很好
-Understood.  -Good.
安吉拉还好吧?
How's Angela?
亚当刚告诉我这不是你的孩子
Adam just told me you're not the mother of this child.
这是谁的孩子?
Who does the baby belong to?
我男友埃里克的
My boyfriend Eric.
埃里克?
Eric?
宾德 他名字是埃里克·宾德
Binder. His name is Eric Binder.
那他为什么不自己照顾女儿?
So why isn't he taking care of his daughter?
因为他前妻首先就会找到他那
Because it's the first place his ex-wife would look.
他前妻有孩子的监护权
His ex-wife has custody of the baby.
几周前 他前妻开始和一个酗酒的男人约会
A few weeks ago, she started seeing this guy with a drinking problem
埃里克发现这人虐待孩子
and Eric found out that this guy was abusing the baby physically.
那他前妻为什么不阻止她男友?
So why isn't the ex-wife stopping the boy-friend?
很显然她不愿承认这个事实
Apparently she's in some kind of denial.
那他为什么不给儿童保护服务中心打电话?
So why doesn't he call child protect services?
埃里克打了
Eric has.
他今早见了社工 但她明天才能解决这个问题
He saw social worker this morning, but she couldn't make it out until tomorrow.
他担心那时就太晚了
He's afraid by then it'll be too late.
等等 那么他绑架了安吉拉?
Wait, so he is kidnapping Angela?
理论上是 但是只有今晚
Technically, but just for tonight.
我不管 克萝伊 绑架儿童可是重罪
I don't care, Chloe. Kidnapping is a felony.
如果你想报警 那就去吧
If you want to call the police, then go ahead and call the police.
但是如果这孩子回到她妈妈身边并且发生了什么不好的事情
But if this child is returned to her mother and something bad happens,
那就是你的责任 好好想想 金
and that's on you. So think about that, Kim.
好好想想
Think about it.
克萝伊 托尼需要你 蔡斯正从波斯塔米塔传送信号过来
Chloe, Tony needs you. Chase's transmitting from Post Mita.
我一会儿就过去
I'll be down there in a minute.
不 他要你马上去
No, he needs you now.
有问题吗?
Is there a problem?
-没 没有  -很好
-No, no problem.  -Good.
回来告诉我她喝了多少奶
Let me know how much of the bottle she takes.
-凯利先生?  -是
-Mr.Kelly?  -Yeah.
请进
Come on in.
这边请
This way, please.
喝点什么?
Drink?
不用了 谢谢
No. Thank you.
我们感谢您能提供帮助 凯利先生
We appreciate your help on this, Mr.Kelly.
我们指你和总统是吗?
We meaning you and the President, right?
是的 这个问题上我可以代表总统
I am representing the president on this, yes.
那么...
So...
你想知道什么?
What can I tell you?
你可以告诉我事情的真相
You can tell me what really happened.
你认为发生了什么?
What do you think happened?
我认为...
I think...
艾伦12年前开车撞死了您女儿
Alan Milican was driving the car that hit and killed your daughter 12 years ago.
我...
I...
我不知道
I wouldn't know.
您作证说什么都没看到 但我认为您看到了
You've testified that you didn't see anything but I think you did
而且我认为你看到的与米利肯有关
and I think what you saw implicates Milican.
您女儿死后3周
3 weeks after your daughter's death,
在航海商业银行开了个你的帐户 并存进了一大笔钱
an account was set up in your name at Maritime Bank and a large deposit was made.
那是封口费 对吗?
That was to keep your mouth shut, wasn't it?
这是一个让真相大白的机会
This is a chance for you to set everything right.
是的
Yeah.
我看到米利肯那晚开着车
I saw Milican driving the car that night,
我看到了车牌和整个经过
got the license plate and everything.
但当我...
But when I...
告诉警察的时候 他把我带到一边
told that to the cop he takes me aside
他说
he says
你女儿已经死了
your daughter is dead.
无可挽回了
Nothing you can do about that now.
但如果你什么也不说
But if you keep your mouth shut,
这儿...
There is...
这儿有笔钱 很大一笔
There is a payoff, a big one.
所以...
So...
我说我没看到是谁撞死了我女儿
I said I didn't see who killed my daughter.
我收了那些沾满血的钱
It was blood money and I took it.
凯利先生
Mr.Kelly
凯利先生 我们有个新闻发布会
Mr.Kelly, we're gonna have a press conference
你有机会把真相告诉所有人
and you are gonna have a chance to tell your story to everyone.
我不会白做这件事的 帕默尔夫人
I'm not gonna be doing this for nothing, Mrs.Palmer.
好的 没关系 你想要多少钱...?
Okay, that's alright. How much money do you...?
不 我不要钱 我已经为此犯过错了
No, I don't want money that I've already made the mistake.
好吧 对不起
Okay, I'm sorry,
那你想要什么?
then what do you want?
我的儿子...
My son...
我唯一活着的孩子
My only living child.
他... 他被判无期徒刑
He is... he is doing a prison term in life sentence.
我要总统赦免他
I want the president to pardon him.
他因为什么入狱?
What was he convicted for?
谋杀
Murder.
他是我的全部
He's all I've got.
你让我儿子出狱
You get the man out of prison
那我就把事实告诉任何想知道那晚真相的人
and I tell anyone who wants to listen what really happened that night.
我不管拉姆怎么想
I don't care what Ramon thinks,
我知道你还在为反恐局工作
I know you're still working with CTU.
你什么都不懂
You don't know anything.
我跟拉姆现在恰好利益一致
My interest happened to coincide with Ramon's at this moment
他知道这一点
and he knows it.
你也许能让所有人相信你 但我不相信
You may have convinced everybody else of that, but I don't believe it.
你最好闭嘴
You keep shutting your mouth off
否则你会为此丢命的
or you're gonna get yourself killed.
无所谓 一旦拿到病毒 他会杀了我们俩的
Doesn't matter. Once he gets the virus, he's gonna kill us both.
解开手铐 她该走了
Uncuff her. She needs to get going.
拿上公事包
Get the briefcase.
如果有什么不对劲 先杀了她
If there's trouble, kill her first.
她跟萨拉扎兄弟的一个保镖一起
She's got one of the Salazars' bodyguard with her.
米歇尔 让大家各就各位
Michelle, send the teams to their final marks.
所有人准备好 行动了
Everybody gets set, this is it.
萨拉扎的人离我300米远
Salazar's men are holding about 300 meters from my location.
埃德蒙兹还在那里
Edmunds' still on point.
没有任何行动
There's been no activity.
确保特种部队严格按照规程办事
Make sure the delta commanders in the field follow protocols straight.
阿尔梅达
Almeida.
我是金 我需要跟你私下谈谈
It's Kim. I need to talk to you in private.
现在吗?
Right now?
是 关于克萝伊的
Yeah. It's about Chloe.
很重要
It's important.
好吧 技术1部见
Alright. Tech one.
有情况通知我
Keep me posted.
你想让我赦免这个人的儿子的谋杀罪名
You want me to pardon this man's son of convicted murder.
我知道我要求的很多 大卫 但是...
I know I'm asking a lot David, but...
除非你豁免凯利儿子的罪
unless you pardon Kelly's son for that crime,
否则他不会帮我们的
he's not gonna help us.
那他打算怎么帮我们?
Then how exactly is he supposed to help us.
12年前凯利曾被买通 没有指控米利肯的罪行
12 years ago, Kelly was paid off not to come forward as a witness against Milican.
他目睹了什么?
What did he witness?
米利肯酒后驾车 撞死了他女儿
Milican killing his daughter while driving drunk then drove off.
肇事逃逸
Hit and run.
凯利是唯一目睹这一切的人
Kelly was the only one who saw it.
但米利肯的人在警察备案前找到了他
Then Milican's people got to him before the police report was filed.
他愿意为此发誓吗?
Will he swear to this?
你所需做的只是赦免他儿子
All you have to do is pardon the son.
他的名字是帕特里克 凯利
His name is Patrick Kelly.
他被判无期徒刑 已经服刑4年了
He's already served 4 years of a life sentence.
我不知道 雪莉 我得想想再和你谈
I don't know, Sherry. I'll have to get back to you on this.
尽快 好吗?
Just hurry, okay?
你怎么想?
What do you think?
你知道我怎么想的 你不该卷入这件事里 大卫
You know what I think. You shouldn't be involved in this, David.
向Mllican让步吧 接受我的辞呈
Give in to Mllican, accept my resignation,
他就会...
and he'll back off...
我告诉过你
I told you
我不是米利肯的玩偶
I am not Milican's puppet.
我不会让他来主宰我的决定
And I will not let him dictate my decisions.
对 但你前妻正说服你 赦免谋杀犯作为交换条件
Right, but you will let your ex-wife convince you to grant quid pro quo pardon to a convicted murderer.
大卫 她才回来才几小时 看看都发生了什么
David, she's only been back in your life for a few hours and look what's happening.
我想获益的人是你吧
I would think you're being favored of what she's being proposing
那你就滥用你的职权吗?
that you would be abusing the power of your office.
绝对不能 大卫 绝对不能 这是错的
Absolutely not, David. Absolutely not, it is wrong.
你曾想让我贿赂安妮的前夫呢
When you wanted me to pay hush money to Anne's ex-husband,
那个就是对的?
that was justified.
区别是...
The differences is that...
大卫 我以你的利益为重 你知道的
David, I have your best interest in heart, you know that.
抱歉提醒你 雪莉总是在做不正确的事
Now I'm sorry, but Sherry has a wrong that she always has.
谢谢你的
Your loyalty
坦率直言
which I am grateful for,
但这不能改变事情
does not change the fact
如果有人想要玩阴招
if someone wants to get down in the mud,
我们就要以其人之道 还治其人之身
the only way to fight back is to get down in with him.
那么你同意赦免了?
So you're gonna grant the pardon?
我还不知道该怎样做
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
好了 金 怎么回事?
Okay, Kim, what is it?
托尼 有些事情你应该...
Tony, there's something you need to...
是关于克萝伊的孩子吗? 我现在没空管这件事
Is this about Chloe's baby, I don't have time to deal with it right now.
这不是她的孩子
It's not her baby.
克萝伊没有孩子
Chloe does not have a baby,
坦白的讲我认为她有妄想症
and frankly I think she is delusional.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
听着 克萝伊没有孩子
Look, Chloe does not have a child.
我问她时 她说这是他男友的孩子
I confronted her, and she said that this was her boyfriend's baby
她说孩子受到虐待 生母置之不理
and the mother of this child was letting her get abused.
但是 托尼 我跟儿童保护服务中心联系过
But Tony I spoke to child protect services,
他们说他们未接到类似的儿童虐待求助
and they said there was no abuse claim filed.
-你确定?  -我确定
-Are you sure?  -Positive.
你发现这个后跟克萝伊说过吗?
Have you talked to Chloe since you found this out?
没有 我之前问她的时候 她显得仓皇失措
No, when I confronted her, she was on the verge of losing it.
瞧 这正是我所担心的
Look, this is what I am worried about.
我认为她情绪十分不稳
I think she's unstable.
金
Kim,
我需要你暂时把这件事放一放
I need you to take a step back here.
我父亲和蔡斯的性命 都掌握在她手里
My father and Chase's life are in her hands.
这正是我们现在不能有任何举措的原因
That's exactly why we can't do anything about this right now.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
听着 克萝伊是我们现在唯一的救命稻草
Look, Chloe's our only lifeline on what's going down there.
她是这里唯一能过滤出蔡斯发给我们音频的人
She's only one in this office capable of filtering audio stream chase's sending us.
-如果克萝伊情绪不稳...  -但是我们现在没有可代替她的人
-If Chloe is unstable...  -But we don't have an alternative right now.
我们必须让她继续工作
We've got to keep her in place.
那这个孩子怎么办?
What about the baby?
不管她父母是谁 他们现在肯定已经急疯了
Whoever her parents are, they must be going out of their minds right now.
你要照顾这个孩子直到行动结束
You're gonna take care of that baby till this operation is over.
我不想克萝伊分心
I do not want Chloe to be distracted.
嘿 这件事我也不高兴
Hey, I'm not happy about this either.
我们就希望克萝伊能坚持工作
Just hope Chloe holds together,
我们一得到病毒就处理这个孩子的事
we'll deal with the baby once we get possession of the virus.
凯利先生?
Mr. Kelly?
等等 我听到了什么
Hold on, I hear something.
有车过来了
There's a car approaching.
托尼 蔡斯报告说有车靠近
Tony, Chase's reporting a car approaching.
萨拉扎的人已严阵以待
Salazar's men are sitting tight.
还没看见阿马多尔的人和其他车辆
There's no sight of Amador's men and no other vehicles.
蔡斯...
Chase...
我看到车了...
I've got a visual...
两个人
Two men in sight
阿马多尔和他的保镖
It's Amador and his bodyguard.
拉姆
Ramon,
阿马多尔到了
Amador's arriving.
他们正下车
They're exiting the car.
阿马多尔拿了个手提箱
Amador's got a case in hand.
特种部队离他们有多远?
How far is delta?
90秒能到
90 seconds away.
没确定是病毒前 不准任何人行动
No one makes a move until we're sure it's the virus.
-明白吗?  -明白
-Understood?  -Understood.
-你带来了吗?  -是
-Do you have it?  -Yes.
很好
Good.
银行转帐准备好了吗?
The transfer protocols for the funds in place with the bank?
我检查过病毒后立马给你转账
I'll transfer the funds once I verify the virus.
让我看看病毒吧
So let's see it.
看起来他要把病毒拿出来了
Looks like he's gonna get the virus out.
他从手提箱里拿出了个罐子
He's taking out a canister from the case.
他正打开盖子
He's unscrewing the lid.
确认病毒需要5分钟
It should take about 5 minutes to confirm it's the virus.
见鬼 我们没有足够的音频过滤器了
Damn it, we don't have enough audio filters.
82街有个实验室 能用那个吗?
There's a lab on 82 street, should I use it?
好
Yeah.
帕默尔先生 我是托尼·阿尔梅达
Mr.Palmer, this is Tony Almeida.
告诉我最新情况 托尼
Give me an update on this, Tony.
病毒交易还没开始
The exchange of the virus hasn't happened yet.
但我们认为很快就会发生
But we expect it going down at any moment.
托尼 国防部想出马抓获病毒 但我相信用不着他们出手
Tony, the pentagon's furious to have the plague captured but I'm sure we don't have to play that way.
你们反恐局的仨个头儿 又在秘密行动
Now this operation again is a secret between 3 CTU agents
我可以预言
and again I will give it a rate.
事情结束后 总统会追究你们仨的责任
When this is over, the President will hold all 3 of you accountable.
我明白 先生
I understand, sir.
如果你打电话来只是为了训斥我 那太不合时宜了
But if you're just calling to reprimand me, you're doing this both undeserved.
我现在要专心行动
I need to focus on this operation.
这个行动 规模有多大?
This operation, how large is it?
我们派了十几个特种部队队员 把守在周边待命准备行动
We've had a dozen of delta teams in the area waiting for the signal to go in.
人手够吗?
Will that be sufficient?
只能这些人
It has to be.
再多派人的话 很容易被发现
Any more bodies down there, we're rather being spotted.
告诉我到底会发生什么?
Tell me exactly what's gonna happen.
我们没有这个时间了 先生
We don't have time for this, sir.
托尼 你要求总统支持你 他做到了
Tony you've asked the president to support you, and then he has.
现在你又把他凉一边 他要知道计划是什么
Now you put him away and he wants to know what the plan is.
迈克尔 阿马多尔 那个卖家
Michale Amador, the seller,
会把病毒交给尼娜·迈尔斯
will hand the virus over to Nina Myers.
他不知道尼娜·迈尔斯现在受我们控制
He doesn't know that Nina Myers is now under our control.
一旦交易完成 特种部队就行动
Once the exchange happens, the delta team's to move in.
拿到病毒 逮捕尼娜·迈尔斯 迈克尔 阿马多尔和拉姆·萨拉扎
Secure the virus, take Nina Myers, Michael Amador, Ramon Salazar into custody.
听起来一切都得非常完美才行
Sounds like a awful lot of things are gonna have to go perfectly.
是这样的
That's true.
我们非常肯定我们已经做好准备
We're pretty sure we've our bases covered.
非常肯定也不够好
Pretty sure isn't good enough.
你要确保万无一失
You make this happen.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
好 我们开始
Okay, we're on.
蔡斯 进展如何?
Chase, what's going on.
看起来他们要完成确认了
It looks like they're about to get confirmation.
匹配
Signatures match.
确认是病毒 重复 确认是病毒
It's the virus. I repeat it. It is the virus.
特种部队行动
Send delta in.
特种部队 行动 快 快
Delta, gin the perimeter. Go, go.
我拿着吧...
I'll take that...
直到收到钱
until the funds are in place
转账
Transfers.
现金转账至651911374
Funds transfer locator 651911374
等待确认
Waiting to confirm.
你的银行打电话来确认现金的转账
Your bank's on the phone to confirm the transfer of the funds.
嗯?
Yes?
651911374已确认
651911374 verified.
-谢谢  -不客气
-Thank you.  -You're welcome.
交易结束
Our business is done.
祝你好运
Good luck.
阿马多尔离开了大楼
Amador's out of the building.
装病毒的手提箱留给了尼娜
He's left the case containing the virus with Nina.
他们开车朝北边去了
They are in a car turning around heading north.
-派一队特种部队去拦截他  -好
-Have a delta unit pick him up.  -Okay.
他们已经在路上了
Unit's on their way.
她正把手提箱带给鲍尔
She's carrying the case to Bauer.
-听不清?  -尼娜·迈尔斯...
-What is that?  -Nina Myers...
尼娜带着病毒离开什么的
Certain things Nina's leaving with the virus
出什么问题了?
What is wrong with this?
克萝伊 频道转移了
Chloe, the channel's migrating.
我知道 我们调到卫星8号
I know, we're switching to a sat 8
现在调?
in the middle of a meet?
究竟怎么回事?
What the hell is going on here?
我只能听到静电噪音
All I'm getting is static.
很快就好
It'll be fine in a second.
你在干什么? 快调回卫星3号
What are you doing, switching back to sat 3.
-不  -你疯了吗?
-No.  -Are you crazy?
卫星3号已经溢出了 我评估软件时注意到这个漏洞的...
Sat 3 is out of range. I noticed the glitch in its realized software...
必须调到卫星8号 否则会失去信号的
Have to switch over, otherwise we'll lost it.
蔡斯 你听到了吗?
Chase, do you copy?
你现在应该能清楚听到
You should be getting a clear signal now.
蔡斯 你听到了吗?
Chase, do you copy?
是 收到
Yeah, I copy.
尼娜仍在监视中 她朝大楼走去
Nina's still in visual range, she's heading towards the building.
特种部队还有50秒赶到
Delta's 50 seconds away.
走吧
Let's go.
做得好
Good job.
拉姆 我们该走了
Ramon, we should go.
不 杰克 我不需要你了
No, Jack. I don't need you anymore.
他要杀了他
He's gonna kill him.
特种部队来不及赶到
Delta team will not be getting there in time.
拉姆 我们说好了的
Ramon, we had a deal.
我弟弟因为你而死的
My brother died because of you.
因为你...
Because of you...
蔡斯...
Chase...
蔡斯 说话
Chase, come in.
托尼 特种部队到了
Tony, Delta 's here.
我行动了
I'm moving in.
拉姆·萨拉扎带着病毒在逃
Ramon Salazar's on the move with the virus.
重复 他带着病毒
Repeat, he has the virus.
他在建筑的西侧
He's at the west wing of the building.
杰克在追捕他
Jack's in pursuit.
你们俩个跟我走 所有人继续追捕
You two, go with me. All men in pursuit.
重复 萨拉扎带着病毒
Repeat, Salazar has the virus.
喂
Hello.
喂 朱莉娅
Hello, Julia.
我是雪莉 帕默尔
It's sherry palmer.
很抱歉这么晚给你打电话 亲爱的
I'm sorry to call so late, sweetie.
你一个人吗?
Are you alone?
是
Yes.
很晚了 雪莉
It is very late, Sherry.
你打电话来想要做什么?
Why are you calling?
我知道你丈夫对大卫所做的事
Because I know what your husband is doing to David.
我无能为力
I can't do anything about that.
不 那不是真的
No, that's not true.
你只是没理由去帮忙
You mean, you don't see any reason to do anything about it,
但我给你个理由
but I'm gonna give you a reason.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我理解你的处境 朱莉娅
I know your situation, Julia.
我知道艾伦控制你 不让你走
I know Alan's too controlling to let you go.
你也不愿牺牲所拥有的一切而离开
And I know you're not willing to sacrifice everything to get out.
这只是你的猜想 我要挂电话了
You're making a lot of assumptions, and I'm hanging up.
不 我说的是事实 你也知道这一点
No, I'm telling the truth and you know it.
我能帮你 朱莉娅
But I can help you, Julia.
我能帮你离开艾伦
I can help you get away from Alan
不用放弃任何东西
without having to give everything up.
太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
你了解我 朱莉娅
You know me, Julia.
当我说我要怎样的时候
When I say I can make something happen,
你最好相信我能做到
you better believe I can.
你怎么做?
How would you do this?
首先 我们要私下见个面
First of all, we need to meet in person.
什么时候?
When?
必须现在
Has to be now.
我不可能晚上这个时候出去还不引起艾伦的怀疑
I can't leave this house at this time of night without Alan wondering what I'm doing.
那我去找你
Then I'm coming to you.
杰克 别开枪
Jack, hold your fire.
蔡斯?
Chase?
是
Yeah.
你没事吧?
You're alright?
是的 我没事
Yeah, I'm alright.
病毒是首要任务
Our first priority is the virus.
拉姆是第二位的
Ramon is our second.
无论谁看到他都不准开枪
Anybody gets a visual, standing order is do not fire.
明白吗?
Are we clear?
明白
Copy.
看起来他从这条路跑了 但如果我是他我会朝北跑
Looks like he's coming down the path. But if I were him, I'd headed north.
朝北会遇到一条河
Heading north would run into the river.
告诉直升机我们的坐标 让他们河上汇合
Give the chopper our coordinates. Tell them to converge on the river.
再派一对人回到那条路以防他往回跑
Send another team back down the path in case he doubles back.
你们4个去那条路 另外2个跟我来
We want 4 of you down that path, and I want 2 of you with me.
我们走
Let's go.
拉姆拿着病毒向北方位置453.6逃去
Ramon's in possession of the virus, he's headed north position 453.6.
收到 453.6
Roger, 453.6
都结束了 拉姆
It's over, Ramon.
你无路可逃了
There's nowhere else for you to go.
我不会回监狱的
I'm not going back to jail.
那个我们之后再谈
After we settling down, we'll talk about it.
算了 杰克
Stop, Jack.
没什么好谈的
There's nothing to talk about.
把病毒放下
Put the cylinder down.
我不想朝你开枪 快把病毒放下
I don't wanna have to shoot you, just put the cylinder down.
杰克 下命令吧
Jack, say the word.
不到时候
Not now.
雷蒙...
Ramon...
我有特权能够帮你减刑
I have the authority to cut a deal.
我们只是要病毒
All we want is the virus.
把病毒慢慢放下吧
Just put the cylinder down slowly.
拜托 我不想朝你开枪
Please, I don't wanna shoot you.
来
There you go.
慢慢轻轻地把它放地上
Put it on the ground nice and easy.
很好
Good.
趴下!
Get down!
-蔡斯 你没事吧?  -嗯
-Chase, are you alright?  -Yeah.
把你电话给我
Give me your phone.
我是杰克·鲍尔 让我跟阿尔梅达讲话
This is Jack Bauer. Pass me through to Almeida now.
马上
Right away.
-怎么了 杰克?  -我们没拿到病毒
-What's going on, Jack?  -We do not have the virus.
重复 我们没拿到病毒
I repeat, we do not have the virus.
拉姆拿到的病毒罐是炸弹
The cylinder Ramon was carrying was ripped with a bomb.
阿马多尔肯定调包了 我们能找到他吗?
Amador must have switched it, do we have a position on him?
特种部队在跟着他呢 他跑不远的
Delta's on with him. He won't get far.
这一定是阿马多尔的计划 他已经安排好了逃跑路线
It must be Amador's original plan which he sees as rearranged escape route.
提醒特种部队
please advise delta team.
我们在做呢 杰克
We're on it, Jack.
托尼 尼娜·迈尔斯也跑了
Tony, Nina Myers' out there too.
她跟这个有关吗?
Any chance she was involved in this?
没有 炸弹就是给她的
No, the bomb was made for her.
特种部队在你以西2公里处截下了阿马多尔 杰克
Delta has Amador pinned 2 kms west of you, Jack.
收到 我们就过去
Copy that, we're moving.
蔡斯 让你的人做好准备
Chase, get your team ready.
向西2公里 沿着公路
2 kms to west, stick with the road.
特种部队3队...
Up delta 3...
下车 快!
Get out of the vehicle, now!
举起手来
Hands in the air.
动一下 你就死定了
Move a muscle, you're dead.
慢慢地趴在地上
Very slowly, get on the ground.
马上!
Do it now!
走
Go.
托尼...
Tony...
特种部队遭到埋伏全部牺牲了
The delta team has been taken out.
阿马多尔跑掉了
Amador's escaped.
托尼 阿马多尔的手机完全失去信号了
Tony, Amador's cell phone just went completely dead.
杰克.
Jack
杰克 说话
Jack, come in
嗯 我是鲍尔
Yeah, it's Bauer.
阿马多尔伏击了特种部队3队 重复 阿马多尔伏击了特种部队3队
Amador ambushed delta 3, I repeat Amador ambushed delta 3.
那是个圈套
It was a set up.
你能追踪到位置吗?
Do you have a position?
不能 我们用手机信号追踪的
Negative, we're tracking by cell phone signal.
伏击开始时我们就失去信号了
We lost it when the ambush happened.
卫星呢?
What about satellite?
不行 现在没有可视卫星覆盖这个区域
No, there's no visual satellite coverage of this area at this time.
混蛋 收到
Son of a bitch. Copy that.
特种部队3队都牺牲了
Delta 3's been taken out.
他们追踪不到阿马多尔了
They don't have a position on Amador.
你想怎么做?
what do you want to do?
我们必须找到尼娜
We've got to find Nina.
带你的人去高地 我在这掩护你们
Take your team up to the high ground. I'll cover you down here.
好 你们 跟我来
Okay. You guys, come on. We'll find...